paktimes.com 2007-08-29

# Privacy Policy - PakTimes

|  |  | 

PakTimes takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how PakTimes treats personal information that PakTimes collects and receives, including information related to your past use of PakTimes products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.   
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PakTimes does not own or control, or to people that PakTimes does not employ or manage.

Information Collection and Use

\- General  
PakTimes collects personal information when you register with PakTimes, when you use PakTimes products or services, when you visit PakTimes pages or the pages of certain PakTimes partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. PakTimes may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.   
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, and information about you. Once you register with PakTimes and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.   
PakTimes collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.   
PakTimes automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, PakTimes cookie information, and the page you request.   
PakTimes uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

PakTimes does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:   
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with PakTimes under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help PakTimes communicate with you about offers from PakTimes and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.   
We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing PakTimes to collect and use their child's information without consenting to PakTimes sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes;   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;   
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PakTimes's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.   
We transfer information about you if PakTimes is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, PakTimes will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.   
PakTimes displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.   
PakTimes does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.   
PakTimes advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).   
PakTimes works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

Cookies

PakTimes may set and access PakTimes cookies on your computer.   
PakTimes lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to PakTimes's cookies.   
PakTimes uses web beacons to access PakTimes cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with PakTimes products and services. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

\- General  
You can edit your PakTimes Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time.   
New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.   
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the PakTimes service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the PakTimes Newsletter, that are considered part of your PakTimes account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.   
You can not delete your PakTimes account once registered, the account deletion option may be available in future so the privacy statement will be updated.

Confidentiality and Security 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

PakTimes may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PakTimes account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please feel free to contact us at: 

PakTimes.Com  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
58-A, Trust Plaza.  
Gujranwala, 52250  
Pakistan.  
0092 (0)300 421 9314 

Effective Date: March 3, 2006

|  |  |  |    
  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---
